<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BeautyApp</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="ob_title_1">Useful tips for every day for beauty</string>
    <string name="ob_title_2">Different categories to improve your appearance</string>
    <string name="ob_title_3">Read the tips, apply them every day and you will become more and more beautiful</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="categ_1">body</string>
    <string name="categ_2">face</string>
    <string name="categ_3">hair</string>
    <string name="categ_4">makeup</string>
    <string name="categ_5">nails</string>
    <string name="body_1_name">Regular exfoliation for incredibly smooth skin</string>
    <string name="body_1_title">There is nothing comparable to the feeling of soft and smooth skin. Regularly use a scrub or hydrophilic exfoliating oil to remove dead cells, stimulate blood circulation and achieve incredible smoothness.</string>
    <string name="body_2_name">Deep hydration with priority to natural oils</string>
    <string name="body_2_title">Absorbing natural oils such as shea butter, avocado or olive into your skin will leave it feeling intensely hydrated and nourished. These oils strengthen the skin\'s natural barrier and restore its health and elasticity.</string>
    <string name="body_3_name">Heartfelt care</string>
    <string name="body_3_title">When choosing shower gels and soaps, preference should be given to mild formulas to maintain the natural balance of oil and moisture in the skin. This ensures that your skin remains soft and hydrated even after showering.</string>
    <string name="face_1_name">Double clean for unparalleled cleanliness</string>
    <string name="face_1_title">Double cleansing is your path to flawless skin. Start with oil or micellar water to effectively remove makeup and impurities. Then use a gentle cleanser to deep clean your pores. This method helps prevent acne and gives your skin an unearthly glow.</string>
    <string name="face_2_name">Hydration to a new level</string>
    <string name="face_2_title">After cleansing, be sure to moisturize your skin generously. Use products with hyaluronic acid or other moisturizing ingredients to maintain moisture balance and avoid dryness. Moisturizing is the secret to healthy, youthful skin.</string>
    <string name="face_3_name">Sun protection</string>
    <string name="face_3_title">Don\'t forget about sun protection. Regularly use sunscreen with SPF to protect your skin from harmful UV rays, prevent photoaging, and reduce your risk of skin cancer. This is one of the most important steps in facial skin care.</string>
    <string name="hair_1_name">Gentle washing and conditioning</string>
    <string name="hair_1_title">Wash your hair with a mild shampoo suitable for your hair type. After shampoo, use conditioner, applying it only to the ends of your hair to avoid weighing it down. This will help maintain natural volume and shine.</string>
    <string name="hair_2_name">Thermal protection before using thermal devices</string>
    <string name="hair_2_title">If you frequently use a hair straightener, hair dryer, or other thermal devices, be sure to use heat protection products. They will help prevent hair damage and keep it healthy.</string>
    <string name="hair_3_name">Masks and olive oil for intensive nutrition</string>
    <string name="hair_3_title">Use moisturizing hair masks once a week to restore its structure and add shine. Olive oil is also great for deep hydration. Distribute the oil evenly throughout your hair, leave for 30-40 minutes, and then rinse thoroughly.</string>
    <string name="make_1_name">Proper skin preparation before makeup for long-lasting radiance</string>
    <string name="make_1_title">Start by cleansing and moisturizing your skin. Then apply a makeup base to create an even finish and improve the longevity of your makeup. This will help your makeup look fresh throughout the day.</string>
    <string name="make_2_name">Neutral shadows for everyday makeup</string>
    <string name="make_2_title">For a natural and versatile look, use neutral eyeshadow shades. They are suitable for any time of day and accentuate your natural beauty.</string>
    <string name="make_3_name">Fixing makeup</string>
    <string name="make_3_title">Don\'t forget to set your makeup with a setting spray. This will make your makeup last and keep it flawless even during a long day.</string>
    <string name="nails_1_name">Regular care of nails and surrounding skin</string>
    <string name="nails_1_title">Use oils to strengthen your nails and cuticles. Oil massage improves blood circulation and promotes the growth of healthy nails.</string>
    <string name="nails_2_name">Be careful with gel polishes</string>
    <string name="nails_2_title">If you prefer gel polishes, do not overdo it with frequent procedures. Frequently applying and removing gel polish can weaken your nails.</string>
    <string name="nails_3_name">Damage Protection</string>
    <string name="nails_3_title">Wear gloves when working with chemicals or water to prevent nail damage. Also try to avoid excessive use of sharp tools for nail care.</string>
    <string name="favourites">favourites</string>
</resources>